[Disclaimer: Characters, locations,
and all depicted events are fictional
and for entertainment purposes only;
viewer discretion is advised]
[Your Third Series]
Your limbs are all hurt.
How can you go back to living alone?
You're staying with me.
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm Thee,
a caretaker here.
Please take care of me and guide me.
You two are close?
And I cannot be?
It has been a while since I met Mr. Sarm.
All he has been leaving me
every day is a lunchbox
hanging on the fence in the morning.
He must have been so busy
that he had little to no time...
Getting to see
the roof of your house is enough.
Anything I can help you with, Mr. Sarm?
Oh, Little Jam.
It's been so long,
and that's how you say hi?
And...is there anything you need?
Oh...
Do I need to have
something on my mind
to come see you?
Not exactly.
I am just confused
about why you are here.
I'm here to ask you
if the grilled squid
was tasty at all.
The grilled squid.
Oh,
the grilled squid from the green market.
It was pretty good.
Hot
and tasty.
Of course.
You've given your heart to grilled squid.
Didn't you say
boiled crabs were the best?
Weren't they your favorite?
The crabs are upset, you know?
Who says I've lost my heart to that?
For me,
boiled crabs are number one.
Hey.
Hm?
Are you close with Thee now?
Why do you hang out with him so much?
Well, I have been working with Thee lately.
Just "Thee"?
Mm.
Thee.
Of course,
you call everybody else by their names.
Thee,
Song,
and "Wasin."
When will you call me by my name?
When are you going to call me "Sarm"?
The next business day?
Two business days?
Or three business days?
It's okay, Little Jam.
It's fine.
It's getting late;
go and get some rest.
I'm going home.
It's time to leave.
Huh?
Mr. Sarm.
Mr. Sarm again.
What is it?
Have a safe trip home.
Mm.
- Ow!
- Oh!
Mr. Sarm!
What is it?
Are you alright?
I fell into the trap you made.
What trap?
Love trap.
- Ow!
- Hey!
- Hey...
- I'm caught in your love trap.
See?
Oh.
This kind of love trap.
You feel me?
- Ow...
- Hey!
Are you sure you are alright?
I am...alright, of course.
[Your Third Series]
♫Still feeling lonely? Well, you've got me,♫
♫Keeping you busy every day♫
♫I might not be the one you wanted,♫
♫But give it time, you'll love me anyway♫
♫It's your heart, so it's your choice,♫
♫I won't ever stand in your way♫
♫But when they make you blue,♫
♫Can you please let me take care of you?♫
♫I'm here to love you as myself, not as a surrogate♫
♫Let me be your safe space when you need a break♫
♫Who cares if I'm not your first or second?♫
♫At least being your third still counts♫
♫I'm here to love you, no matter who left you with heartache♫
♫Just let me heal your heart, lending you my aid♫
♫Have faith and believe in love once more♫
♫'Cause good love is your Lucky Third♫
♫Your Third, can it be me, love?♫
[Your Third Series]
You are here to drink coffee, Thee?
That's right.
It's got such a great vibe
in the morning here.
That's why I want to drink coffee here.
Care for a cup of coffee, Jam?
It's on me.
I am worried that
I will be late for work this afternoon.
What's there to be afraid of?
You're here with me, you see.
No one would dare say anything,
would they?
Right...
Do you get uncomfortable around me?
Not really.
You are kind and easygoing.
It doesn't feel awkward at all?
Why does it have to be?
Usually,
people are too scared to approach me.
So it all feels awkward to them.
But you...
Consider yourself lucky
because I gave you
a chance to be here with me.
Right.
Mr. Thee sure is easygoing.
But sometimes, he pushes people...
and throws his weight around.
Allow me to ask you something.
As an outsider,
what do you think of Adisuan Farm?
Adisuan Farm began with an orange farm.
Then, it branched out
into several businesses,
such as dining,
tourism,
and hospitality.
It is a true one-stop tourism empire
that is likely to keep growing
steadily.
Do you know that it's all because of me?
Without me,
Adisuan Farm wouldn't have grown,
and there would only be
Uncle Decha's orange farm.
And Mr. Sarm...
Oh, Sarm?
He's just a son of Uncle Decha's mistress.
I'm the real deal.
Know this.
I'm in the same league as Sib, alright?
When Sib has a problem,
he always comes straight to me.
You truly are talented, Thee.
Well, you know?
By the way...
Do you want to be part of this empire?
If you have time, come to my place.
I'll show you my priceless achievements.
I keep a lot of
important things in my office.
Feel free to swing by.
Who do you live with, Thee?
I live alone, actually.
This is Jiranat speaking.
And this is Traiphop speaking.
Is there anything you need, Mr. Sarm?
I've got everything I need,
except your heart.
Did you have dinner?
Tell me if you're worried about me.
And tell me if you have feelings for me.
Are you heading to bed?
Soon, actually.
Please don't.
Stay with me for a bit first.
I'm driving alone, you know?
And I'm scared of ghosts.
Just say hi to them.
They are your friends after all.
Oh...
You and your words.
What did you have for dinner?
Instant noodles.
A crazy day
wrapped around instant noodles.
Have less of that.
Eat some good food.
But they are tasty,
and I enjoy having them.
I enjoy having you, too.
Then why did you scold me over that?
Don't confess to anyone yet, okay?
I'm trying to win you over.
Talking to Mr. Sarm always feels like...
riding a roller coaster,
He teases me one second,
sulks the next,
and then makes me feel things.
Have a safe trip home.
Goodnight.
Right.
♫I only wish you nothing but the best♫
♫Hoping your smile will never fade♫
♫That's all, for I don't wish
to take someone's place♫
Actually...
I no longer see Mr. Sarm as an immature guy.
Perhaps...
I actually like him,
but I do not know
how I feel about him exactly.
The more this keeps dragging on,
the more confusing it gets.
I have to get this mission over with
so that I can move on.
Tonight...
I am going to snoop around
Mr. Thee's place first.
When the time is right,
I will go there for real.
Ow...
Little Jam, are you hurt?
Are you alright...?
The question is for you.
Is your hand hurt?
I'm fine.
Why are you trying to be so inconspicuous?
You've got both a taser
and a flashlight.
It's like you're about to have a fight.
That sounds ridiculous.
So where are you going,
hm?
I got hungry,
so I wanted to
get something to eat.
Oh.
But I got lost,
and I am starving.
Hello.
Aunt Salee, please treat
some wounds at my place.
And...
Please prepare dishes for two.
Right.
I am not going with you.
Fine.
You want to stay here?
Know this.
This area
is infested with water ghosts.
The orange tree spirits are just as scary.
If you stay here,
they'll take your life!
If your neck gets snapped in half,
don't say I didn't warn you.
No need to scare me.
Be honest.
Are you sure you actually lost?
Mm.
Are you certain
that you're not plotting anything?
I am doing nothing.
I'll give you one more chance.
Spit it out.
I said I wasn't plotting anything.
Okay.
But if I catch you lying,
even if it's you,
I won't let it slide.
Why?
If I really am hiding something from you...
That was just a hypothetical situation
and nothing else.
I'd be furious.
I'd be mad at you
for a whole week.
Playing cute?
Wait.
Why?
What do you want?
You can be mad at me for a week if you want,
but you have to forgive me after that, okay?
Wait...
Hold on.
You...
Hey.
What's wrong?
Isn't this just a hypothetical scenario?
Why are you so emotional?
Come.
Let's leave.
This is nothing at all, Mr. Sarm.
It's nothing, Mr. Jam.
Allow me to call it a night, then.
Thank you.
Goodnight, Aunt.
Goodnight.
I told you I was fine.
You were being dramatic.
What do you mean?
Listen.
Isn't it better to know you're fine
than leave it untreated?
How did you end up there anyway?
I was at the mayor's child's wedding,
and I was passing by that area.
That's why I spotted
someone
acting all inconspicuous.
I almost shot you
right there and then.
What were you doing
around my quarters this late?
Why did you not return to your place?
Oh.
I was patrolling.
The farm is vast, you see.
What would happen if a thief sneaked in?
Thus, we need to do
a bit of patrolling, correct?
It's close to New Year.
Do you have plans for your costume?
I actually have nothing in mind.
If you don't,
then
how about we wear matching costumes?
Like what?
Bananas in Pyjamas.
You'll dress as B1,
and I'll dress as B2.
Let's dress up as a pair.
B1 and B2.
But the theme is something spooky.
Spooky.
Mm.
Ghost bananas.
Huh?
That wouldn't fly, would it?
If that's the case,
how about
we exchange gifts?
Do you mean
doing a lucky draw?
Not that.
Like,
you and me,
Jam and Sarm.
Just the two of us.
Mm.
Alright.
Lovely.
Jam.
Hm?
Why does this feel so spooky?
There is nothing to be afraid of.
Who exactly
voted for this theme?
- Boo!
- Whoa!
Doctor Ning-nong!
You scared us.
What ghosts
are you dressing up as?
I am dressing up as a krahang.
What about you, Doctor Ning-nong?
A sheet ghost.
That is a very cool idea.
Oh, boys.
Whoa.
What are you dressing up as?
I can only guess Jam's costume.
I'm dressing up as a sheet ghost.
Oh, right.
What about you?
I'm dressing up as a medium.
I'm here to exorcise a certain ghost.
Be careful of exorcising the wrong ghost.
I won't fail. Don't worry.
I'll be on my way, then.
I have to get ready to be the emcee, too.
Alright.
Shall we play a game?
Over there.
Let's not. Sarm is arriving soon.
Mm.
I can't wait to find out
what ghost Sarm is dressing up as.
Okay, okay.
I will be back, then.
Let me join you, too.
You know how to use a spirit board?
Thee?
I almost could not recognize you.
Am I so handsome
that you almost did not recognize me?
By the way,
have you ever used a spirit board?
I have not, actually.
But I want to give it a try.
Let me show you the ropes.
A spirit board...
is like a tool,
bridging the realm
of the spirits and ours.
It shows us
what they're trying to communicate.
First, place a finger
on the cup like so.
Then, concentrate
and let the spirit
communicate with us.
"D..."
"I..."
"N..."
"E..."
"R..."
"?"
"Dinner?"
"W..."
"I..."
"T-H..."
"M-E-?"
And...
Where do you want to have dinner?
Please have dinner with me
at my place, Jam.
And when?
Let's go with...
Whoa.
Judging by the costume,
we have to make way for him to make an entrance.
A lot of you here might be wondering
what ghost I'm dressing as.
I'm...
A crab spirit!
A round of applause, please!
Make some noise, and I'll give you a raise!
First of all,
Happy New Year to everybody here.
Thank you, everyone,
for taking Adisuan Farm to this point.
An organization can only grow
when
its people grow together.
I'm losing my voice,
so I'll leave it there.
I prefer having the results do the talking.
Thank you.
Hey.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- Hey.
I will hit you back.
Hey.
Little Jam.
It's now the new year,
but I'm still the same old me.
The same goes for me.
You're as cute as always.
And you are as dramatic as usual.
Whoa.
It's a new year now.
Anything you'd like to tell me?
It is nice knowing you.
It's nice to know what love is like, too.
I've got a present for you as well.
But I can't bring it here tonight.
Tomorrow,
you have to go and get it at my place
by yourself.
Understand?
I already have an appointment tomorrow.
It's fine.
Late evening will do.
I can wait, as long as it takes.
But right now,
I have a request
and something to tell you.
What is it?
You.
I...
Hm?
Help me take off this crab suit.
- Oh, come on.
- Pull the claws.
Please?
- Look at me.
Come on. It won't take long.
Come on. Help me.
- I am pulling.
- Hey.
- Three,
- Be careful.
two, one.
Mr. Sarm! Hey!
Mr. Sarm.
Grab... Grab onto my arm.
Sure. I'm alright.
Thank you.
Gosh, the crab suit.
Your hair is a mess.
- Is it?
- Mm.
Do I look handsome, though?
Not sure.
We had quite a rocky start,
didn't we?
But what I want to tell you
is the truth.
Listen carefully, okay?
Don't fall asleep on me.
You seem serious.
Very much so.
No one can be as serious as me.
Are you leading me here
to pull a prank on me?
Hey.
In your eyes,
what am I like?
You are slick,
crazy,
totally over-the-top,
overacting,
and totally unpredictable.
Oh.
In truth,
you did not have to dress up as anything.
Huh?
Because you're haunting me
every day like a pervy ghost.
Oh, Little Jam.
Ow.
Does it hurt that much?
But this man loves you very much.
I love you.
I love you, Little Jam.
♫Time stood still when I met you♫
♫The way you gazed at me too♫
♫Couldn't understand what I felt, I had no clue♫
I love you in every way
a man is capable of loving someone.
I've thought it through.
I don't actually know
when I started to have this feeling,
and I couldn't find an answer either.
By the time I realized it,
I had already fallen for you.
Although it seems like
I don't take things seriously,
let me tell you that
I'm serious when it comes to loving you.
But you told me that I was just a burden.
Can you forgive me, though?
This man
was blind to what truly matters.
You used to call me Snoop.
Oh.
Can I beg for your forgiveness?
I've got flowers
and incense sticks ready.
I was once a foul-mouthed person.
You are allowed to slap me on the lips
as many times as you'd like.
There.
I told you
not to confess to anyone
because I wanted to keep your eyes on me.
I approached you
as a man,
not as your boss's younger brother.
You once only considered me
a Pak Chong branch spouse.
And I'd like to use this opportunity
to get an answer from you.
You once put me at the bottom of the list.
But can I now be your number one?
Let's just say...
If you let me be your number one,
a kiss means it's a yes.
Hold me. I'm going to pass out.
Mr. Sarm!
Mr. Sarm, Mr. Sarm.
Mr. Sarm.
Mr. Sarm...
Are you okay?
I am.
I am very okay.
Of course, I am.
Are you hurt?
I'm very okay. I'm fine.
I thought something happened to you.
It was nothing.
Let's go home.
Right.
♫I'll stay right here by your side, always♫
Can I have another kiss?
You had enough.
Gosh.
Gosh, come on.
"I love you, Little Jam."
His confession still lingers in my mind.
But tonight, I have a mission to take care of.
How will the results turn out, I wonder?
Hello, Song.
Hi there, Jam.
Take a seat.
Thank you.
Where are you off to
at such an early hour?
Isn't today everybody's day off?
It is.
I am here to get some coffee.
Where are you going?
I was just done with my shift.
I am about to go and rest up for a bit.
I am terribly sleepy right now.
Oh, tonight,
there's dinner at the main house.
Sib and PiMai are going there.
Jam... Are you interested in being there?
I am already occupied this evening.
Is that so?
That's a shame, really.
And...
Where are you off to this evening?
Thee's place.
Lately, we have been
working together a lot.
Uh-huh, Thee's place.
Oh.
Last night,
there was a party, wasn't there?
I heard that the theme
was ghost-related, right?
Did you have fun?
You must've looked cute
in your costume.
It was pretty fun.
"I love you, Little Jam."
So...
Sarm...
confessed his love to you, didn't he?
You knew?
Of course, I knew.
Sarm and I are twins, remember?
We keep no secrets from each other.
With that, I had the answer.
I saw right through you.
And...
What did you say?
Am I close to having...
a brother-in-law?
I did not say anything.
I think
you should just say yes.
Thinking about it
already gives me a headache.
You're right.
Excuse me.
Mr. Sarm, would you like to have lunch right now?
I'm good, Aunt.
I...
It's too much to eat anything.
Are you feeling unwell?
Are you having a stomachache?
Do you want me to call a doctor?
It's okay.
I...
I'm extremely fulfilled.
I can just live like this for years
without eating anything.
I'm over the moon right now.
It's like I'm mentally fulfilled.
Hunger means nothing.
I'm overjoyed.
I'll skip lunch.
Right...
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
Good evening, Thee.
Hi.
You look extremely lovely this evening.
No...
You look this lovely every day.
You are also looking good.
Thank you.
Shall we get going, then?
Sure.
This way.
Right.
Alright.
Please take a seat.
Thank you.
Mm...
I didn't actually know...
what kind of food you prefer,
so I made you steak.
Looks very appetizing.
I also...
I do kind of know how to cook.
I poured my heart and soul into it.
I wanted you to give it a try.
Well...
Can I post it on my IG Stories?
Would you mind, Thee?
No problem.
Alright.
Mm...
Would you like to film
some IG Stories with me?
Would it be a good idea?
If your partner got it all wrong,
I am not to blame...
Mm...
Let me tell you something.
Well...
I'm single.
And...
I don't want to be single anymore.
From here,
the view is rather beautiful.
It is, isn't it?
Whenever I'm stressed out,
I'd just sit down and enjoy the view.
Seeing something
I created with my own hands makes me...
feel somewhat proud of myself.
As for me,
all I've been doing is working,
constantly doing this and that.
I haven't caught a break at all.
That is why Adisuan Farm has grown this much.
Right, Jam?
Let me tell you this.
I've done a lot for this empire,
and...
I'm Uncle Decha's only grandson.
So I think...
Adisuan Farm
should belong to me, shouldn't it?
But...
Uncle Decha has heirs, does he not?
The brats at the main house?
Know this.
They're all his problematic children,
especially Sarm.
That brat
is always causing trouble for people
whenever he does something.
Without me,
no one else could've taken
Adisuan Farm this far.
No wonder
someone was hunting him down
when I was tasked with bringing
Mr. Sarm back from Ko Pha-ngan.
It's because
he always causes trouble for others.
He is the worst.
By the way...
Were you involved, too, Jam?
Is it uncomfortable?
Not at all, I guess?
Want to join us?
Come. It'll be nice and cozy.
PiMai, come on.
There's still room for me?
It's fine. Come on.
Hey, wait, kiddo.
You shouldn't.
It's already too hard to breathe.
Okay.
And you shouldn't have said that.
Dad!
It's fine for you two to have some space.
There's still a lot more room left.
Sib,
do you want to have baos with me?
He's probably sick of eating them.
You should find something
to stuff your mouth with, Sarm.
Why?
Worried about me?
You're worried I'd get hungry?
No, not at all.
Go get something to eat,
so you'll stop talking.
Is it wrong that I'm talking?
Of course not,
but it's annoying.
- Sarm.
- It's not.
- Dad loves my voice.
- What do you think, Dad?
Shut it.
- I'm talking to Dad here.
- Hey, that's enough.
Enough already, you two.
Take a breather.
Stop it.
Listen.
Aren't you a bit too obsessed
with your phone, huh?
I'm not.
But I'm obsessed with...
someone I chat with on my phone.
Song.
Huh?
After we're done here,
help me wrap a present at the quarters.
- Wrap a present?
- Yeah.
What present?
How big can it be?
Well, you have to wrap me.
Huh?
Put a ribbon on me, too.
You're nuts.
What are you doing this for?
What?
I want to be Jam's present.
Also...
I want to make it official, too.
Are you serious?
This is cringe.
Sib, are you alright?
I haven't been able to reach Jam,
which is unusual.
What time is it?
It's almost 8 P.M.
Quit it while you can,
asking someone to work overtime.
Humans aren't robots.
Little Jam is this tiny.
"Little Jam," you said?
Let me tell you something.
I always pay him for the overtime.
I know.
I think...
You're a bit out of the loop, Sib.
What am I missing?
Yeah.
I also want to say that
Jam will be with me tonight.
And let me tell you this.
If you need something from him,
discuss it with him later.
You're right.
Sib always overworks Mr. Jam.
- Right, PiMai?
- Goodness me...
I
will have Jam stay here.
I won't give him back either.
- How's that sound?
- PiMai!
Sounds good.
Right?
PiMai.
Take that.
Correct.
I got caught up
in Mr. Sarm's business as well.
At first, we ran
and ended up at a fishing village.
But eventually, the thugs found us.
Now that you know,
please keep this a secret.
Of course.
Uh, by the way...
What's next?
When they found us for the second time,
we would have escaped if we had tried,
but Mr. Sarm
did not take the situation seriously,
so they caught us and put us on their boat.
As I've said, Jam.
Sarm is incompetent.
He couldn't even handle
a handful of thugs himself.
On top of that, the boat they were using
was so old that
if he chose to make an escape,
he would've gotten away.
A handful of men.
An old boat.
Was that what you said, Thee?
You heard me.
Though there were only a few of them,
they all looked like badasses.
If the underlings were already that cool,
I wonder how cool the boss would be.
I think the boss must look like
the main character from Prison Break.
He is so my type.
"Your type," you said?
Yes.
Take a seat.
Have a seat.
Mm...
Jam.
I think...
I've got something
to tell you.
It's a secret, too.
Listen up.
It was me
who sent those men to get rid of Sarm
once and for all.
Sarm doesn't deserve
to rule the Adisuan empire.
Don't you agree?
You truly deserve to rule Adisuan Farm.
By the way...
I'm this talented,
and you're not interested in me?
What do you mean by that, Thee?
What I'm saying is this...
I'm interested in you.
I like you.
Do you know that I've been wanting to
get to know you since I first saw you,
hm?
And aside from that...
What is your type, Jam?
I have no preferences.
I love whoever I feel like loving.
Mm.
Come on, Jam.
Mm...
Just tell me. I'm curious to find out.
I love the type of person who is cheerful
and knows when to have fun
and be serious.
You hit the nail on the head.
The type of person you just described,
I think...
it's basically me.
Wouldn't you agree?
Oh...
What does this mean?
What does this mean,
hm?
No answer?!
Come here!
Are you going to spit it out,
huh?
I'm asking you what the fuck that means.
Come here.
What the fuck is this shit, huh?!
How dare you?!
Think you can fool me, huh?!
I adored you, Jam.
Taking my phone from me changes nothing.
I have already made hundreds of copies
of the audio files.
If I disappear for more than two hours,
a voice message will be sent to
Mr. Sib automatically.
You are doomed either way.
Your best bet...
is to confess your crime.
You still have time.
Confess my crime?
You want me to confess?!
If you...
If you can't make it out of this place,
no one will ever know
what we discussed here.
About you sending men
to get rid of Mr. Sarm,
though Mr. Sarm knew nothing,
Mr. Sib knew all about it.
All that he needs is evidence.
Evidence?
You mean this?
Sheesh.
That is no toy.
You will pay for it,
including for hurting me.
I will not let this slide.
I will have my revenge.
You want to have your revenge?!
Before you can do that,
how about you make sure
you can survive this night,
huh?
What should I do with you, Jam?
Oh.
Well...
How about this?
I will bring your laptop here,
and you have to get rid of the audio files.
Every single one of them.
Then,
I'll let you go.
But after that,
you have to behave.
Don't do anything stupid.
You know that
you can't escape from me, don't you?
With what you have done to me,
do you think I can?
It's nice that you know that.
- Ow!
- Hey!
Why are you so hard to get,
huh?!
Know this!
Don't.
Don't do anything stupid,
okay?
- Ah!
- Whoa!
The gunshot
was from the very end of the farm.
Maybe it came from Thee's place.
Thee's... Thee's place?
Mm.
This means that
Jam is in danger.
Huh?!
- What do you mean?
- What?
This morning,
I met Jam,
and he told me that
he's meeting Thee at his place tonight.
Song, contact the doctors.
Sarm.
Sib, if you wouldn't mind,
please go to my place.
If Jam comes back and doesn't see me,
at least he'll see you there.
Come on!
Ow...
Wait here.
I'll be right back.
Jam! Jam!
Jam.
Mr. Sarm, you must listen to me.
I now know who sent those men
to hunt you down back at Ko Pha-ngan.
It was Mr. Thee.
He was behind it all.
I have the evidence.
I have the audio recording.
But he threw my phone and broke it.
But do not worry.
I have sent the recording to Mr. Sib.
You do not have to worry about it now.
That bastard did this to you?
Call Sib.
He'll take you to the doctor.
Can you still drive?
Where are you going?
I'll be right back.
Mr. Sarm.
Mr. Sarm!
Hey!
I was just...
Asshole!
This one's for hitting Jam in the face!
Ow!
And that one
is for choking Jam!
Ow!
You...
And this one is for threatening Jam!
I never let a single mosquito bite him.
I took care of him with utmost care.
And who the fuck do you think you are
to hurt my beating heart?!
Jam was trespassing.
You first said it was a thief!
You're the most deceitful bastard ever.
It's a damn shame that I trusted you!
You've never wondered
why Little Jam came to you for the truth?!
Wasn't it because you've done
some scummy shit in the past?!
Huh?!
Stop.
Hey.
Sarm.
Why would I send someone to kill you, huh?
I have said nothing,
so why jumped the fucking gun?!
You worthless piece of shit!
If you weren't a son of Uncle Decha,
you wouldn't have made it this far!
Is that what you've always been thinking of me?
You're damn right.
What else do you expect, huh?!
Insult me all you want,
but calling me "worthless" is way out of line!
It's someone like you
whom I call worthless.
You're a worthless piece of shit!
Ha!
Whoa!
Ah!
Stop it, Thee!
If you hurt Mr. Sarm in any way,
I will shoot!
A petty threat from a little boy
won't fucking stop me!
Why didn't you listen?!
You're so stubborn.
Your mission has ended.
It's time for you to return to Bangkok.
I'm
upset at both of them.
Come and take Jam home.
Oh, Ning-nong.
I have something to tell you, Sarm.
♫Kiss, kiss♫
♫You♫
♫Can I kiss you?♫
♫Kiss, kiss♫
♫That's all I've ever wanted♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫Can I give a cutie like you a kiss? (Ohhhh, oh)♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?
(Just you, only you, can it be you?)♫
♫You♫
♫Just a bit more (Hoo, woo)♫
♫Can I kiss you one more time?♫
♫Can I give you one more kiss?♫
♫I'm not gonna lie (Hoo, woo))♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou
(If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind)♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou, ou
♫You, ou, ou, ou
(If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind)♫
♫You, ou, ou, ou♫
♫If I can't kiss you now, I'd lose my mind♫
[Your Third Series]